

HAMJAKMA REANG

CONTACT

Phone 8787339008

Email

hamjakmarb@gmail.com

Address

JP Nagar 7th phase, Nataraj layout, 560078, Bangalore.

SKILLS

- Emotional Intelligence
- Communication
- Digital marketing
- MS Word & MS Excel
- leadership
- Content creation & Audio
 Visual production

LANGUAGE

English
95%

Hindi
70%

Achievements

-Youtube Silver Play Button

ABOUT ME

Ambitious and optimistic individual with excellent time management skills, always up for meeting new people and open to challenges which gives experiences and shapes personality. A triple major graduate student and content creator with capability of handling multiple projects simultaneously.

EDUCATION

• Christ University, Bangalore.

BA Economics, Media Studies and Political Science. (2019-2022)

Extracurricular activities:

- -High Soprano Singer (Christ University Choir).
- -Stage management and part of Public Relations team. (Raabta'2019- College fest organized by Media Studies department of Christ University).

Courses:

- -Music theory comprehensive part 1,2 and 3 in Udemy by Jason Allen. (Sept. 2021)
- The Science of Well-Being by Yale University. (Feb. 2022)

EXPERIENCE

- Digital marketing internship
 May 2021 to July 2021
 at Serri Club(@serri club)
- Social media content creation 2017- Present

Social media handles:

Instagram: hamjakmareangmusic Youtube: Hamjakma Reang

OTHER INTERESTS:

- Make up
- Skin care
- Fashion